<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Peter&#39;s weblog</title>
    <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Peter&#39;s weblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 20:47:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Audio</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/blog/audio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 20:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/blog/audio/</guid>
      <description>This is a test page for audio. All files need to go in the static directory. And the html code for inbeded player needs to be added to the body of blog page and linked to the file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roger Waters - on - RT - The Us and Uk Are Trying to Kill Julian Assange</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/roger-waters-on-rt-the-us-and-uk-are-trying-to-kill-julian-assange/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 14:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/roger-waters-on-rt-the-us-and-uk-are-trying-to-kill-julian-assange/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By Kevin Reed
2 November 2019&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Famed rock music artist Roger Waters gave an extensive and significant interview to the television network Russia Today (RT) on October 25 in which he denounced the continued illegal imprisonment of Julian Assange and reiterated his call for the freedom of the WikiLeaks publisher and founder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julian Assange, who founded WikiLeaks in 2006 and published extensive proof of US war crimes in the Middle East and other corruption around the world, is currently being held at Belmarsh prison in London. Although he has broken no laws and not been convicted of any crime, Assange is being held in advance of being handed over—in blatant contravention of international law—to the United States to face 18 charges, including violation of the Espionage Act of 1917.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guns and Butter - Rescuing the Banks Instead of the Economy - Michael Hudson</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/post/guns-and-butter-rescuing-the-banks-instead-of-the-economy-michael-hudson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 22:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/post/guns-and-butter-rescuing-the-banks-instead-of-the-economy-michael-hudson/</guid>
      <description>2018 marks the 10th anniversary of the stock market crash of 2008; the current financial malaise is the result of the bank bailouts, not the crash; an over-indebted economy cannot be saved unless the banks fail; debt deflation; the magic of compound interest; how pension funds, state and local governments adversely affected by the bank bailouts; growth of the financial extraction FIRE sector (finance, insurance and real estate); quantitative easing; asset price inflation; wealth concentrated at the top in Roman antiquity led to the Dark Age; Eurozone imposition of austerity Greek style; tariffs, economic sanctions and isolationism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trade Unions &#39;Rich and Cowardly&#39; - FRFI! Newspaper</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/trade-unions-rich-and-cowardly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 13:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/trade-unions-rich-and-cowardly/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Created: Thursday, 31 October 2019 - Written by Robert Clough&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delivering his keynote speech to the 2019 TUC Congress in September, supposed left-wing trade union leader and TUC President Mark Serwotka plaintively asked of the future ‘Will we end up just observing the rise of the far right, including our current government? Will we watch, horrified, the further decimation of our public services? Will we look fearfully at the rise of racism and hate? Will we be passive witnesses of the growth of a climate emergency?’ All the evidence for the past ten years points to one answer – yes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The British trade union movement stood by as wages were slashed following the 2008 financial crisis, it has remained passive in the face of an onslaught on working conditions, and has pointedly protected Labour councils as they took an axe to jobs and services at the behest of the Tory austerity programme. When Serwotka concluded ‘How can we step up to face the scale of these challenges? For Congress, I hope you agree – stand up to them we must!’, it was no more than braggadocio. British trade unions are not fighting organisations of the working class, and nor are they intended to be.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guns &amp; Butter - Exposing the 9/11 Deception - Christopher Bollyn</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/exposing-the-9-11-deception-christopher-bollyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 13:09:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/exposing-the-9-11-deception-christopher-bollyn/</guid>
      <description>Christopher Bollyn in NYC on 9&amp;frasl;11; companies hired to do ground zero &amp;ldquo;clean-up&amp;rdquo;; hot spots; analysis of nuclear footprint at ground zero; analysis of smoke and the particle effect that caused debilitating illnesses in NYC; the mysterious &amp;ldquo;final load&amp;rdquo; moved out of ground zero; same criminal network behind 9&amp;frasl;11 and Jeffrey Epstein; Ronald Lauder; privatization programs; Ehud Barak; University of Alaska Fairbanks study on WTC 7; Commissioner of the Franklin Square and Munson Fire District calling for a new investigation; government officials conduct the cover-up; Khalid Sheikh Mohammed; surveillance state; dystopia created by 9&amp;frasl;11 attacks; motivation of 9&amp;frasl;11 to create the war on terror; Bollyn&amp;rsquo;s new book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Harvey&#39;s - Anti-Capitalist Chronicles: Alienation - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/post/anti-capitalist-chronicles-alienation-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 18:37:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/post/anti-capitalist-chronicles-alienation-part-2/</guid>
      <description>David Harvey&amp;rsquo;s - Anti-Capitalist Chronicles: Alienation - Part 2
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Harvey&#39;s - Anti-Capitalist Chronicles: Alienation - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/post/anti-capitalist-chronicles-alienation-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 18:37:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/post/anti-capitalist-chronicles-alienation-part-1/</guid>
      <description>David Harvey&amp;rsquo;s - Anti-Capitalist Chronicles: Alienation - Part 1
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welfare state alive in scotland but waning elsewhere - UN poverty expert</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/welfare-state-alive-in-scotland-but-waning-elsewhere-un-poverty-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 15:15:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/welfare-state-alive-in-scotland-but-waning-elsewhere-un-poverty-expert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A UN poverty expert has said Scotland is on “a very different trajectory” to the rest of the UK when it comes to social security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Philip Alston, UN Special Rapporteur on extreme poverty and human rights, said the “spirit” of the welfare state is “alive and humming” north of the border, but is “waning” elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The international human rights law professor visited the UK last year to produce a report which found policies of austerity introduced in 2010 were continuing to have “tragic social consequences”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also claimed the Scottish government’s attempts to reduce the impact of social security changes – such as the two-child benefit cap – were not sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking at an event at the University of Edinburgh, he said: “Scotland is spending a lot of money on mitigation, mitigating measures that they see as the least humane policies that come from London.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“All of this indicates that Scotland is – at least for now – on a very different trajectory than England when it comes to the social protection of its population.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guns &amp; Butter - The Post 9/11 Era</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/the-post-9-11-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 19:33:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/the-post-9-11-era/</guid>
      <description>Posted on September 30th, 2019
Guest: Michel Chossudovsky
We discuss the broader geopolitical ramifications of the September 11th terrorist attacks, including the attack on Afghanistan, the Global War on Terror, and the Western Military Alliance support for the terrorists; attack on Afghanistan prepared long before 9&amp;frasl;11; Osama bin Laden an intelligence asset; Bushes, et.al., business partners with the bin Ladens; earlier history of Afghanistan before the Soviet intervention; Afghanistan becoming a modern nation; US imperialism the destroyer of countries; assassination of the leader of the Northern Alliance, Ahmad Shah Massoud; the cultivation of opium poppy; Afghanistan a major transport corridor for oil and gas; mineral resources; Islamic fundamentalism a strategy of US intelligence to indoctrinate and recruit jihadists; extension of al Qaeda worldwide; US losing control of Afghanistan and Pakistan to China; pre-emptive nuclear war doctrine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK - More than a million welfare benefit sanctions imposed against disabled people</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/uk-more-than-a-million-welfare-benefit-sanctions-imposed-against-disabled-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 13:25:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/uk-more-than-a-million-welfare-benefit-sanctions-imposed-against-disabled-people/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By Dennis Moore
13 March 2018&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New data reveals the relentless attack on disabled benefit claimants in the last decade. The study found that more than 900,000 Job Seeker’s Allowance (JSA) claimants, who reported a disability, have been financially sanctioned since May 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also sanctioned were 110,000 claimants of Employment and Support Allowance (ESA), a benefit paid to someone who is sick, and placed in the “work related activity group” (WRAG). A further 140,000 sanctions were applied, but later cancelled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A sanction is applied to someone’s benefit when a claimant is deemed not to have met part of the stated “conditionality” for claiming that benefit. This can include missing an appointment, or not applying for enough jobs in a given time scale.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Peter&#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/about/</guid>
      <description>The put content in yet, peter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>