<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Peter&#39;s weblog</title>
    <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Peter&#39;s weblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 18:37:53 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>David Harvey&#39;s - Anti-Capitalist Chronicles: Alienation - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/anti-capitalist-chronicles-alienation-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 18:37:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/anti-capitalist-chronicles-alienation-part-2/</guid>
      <description>David Harvey&amp;rsquo;s - Anti-Capitalist Chronicles: Alienation - Part 2
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Harvey&#39;s - Anti-Capitalist Chronicles: Alienation - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/anti-capitalist-chronicles-alienation-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 18:37:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/anti-capitalist-chronicles-alienation-part-1/</guid>
      <description>David Harvey&amp;rsquo;s - Anti-Capitalist Chronicles: Alienation - Part 1
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welfare state alive in scotland but waning elsewhere - UN poverty expert</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/welfare-state-alive-in-scotland-but-waning-elsewhere-un-poverty-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 15:15:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/welfare-state-alive-in-scotland-but-waning-elsewhere-un-poverty-expert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A UN poverty expert has said Scotland is on “a very different trajectory” to the rest of the UK when it comes to social security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Philip Alston, UN Special Rapporteur on extreme poverty and human rights, said the “spirit” of the welfare state is “alive and humming” north of the border, but is “waning” elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The international human rights law professor visited the UK last year to produce a report which found policies of austerity introduced in 2010 were continuing to have “tragic social consequences”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also claimed the Scottish government’s attempts to reduce the impact of social security changes – such as the two-child benefit cap – were not sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking at an event at the University of Edinburgh, he said: “Scotland is spending a lot of money on mitigation, mitigating measures that they see as the least humane policies that come from London.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“All of this indicates that Scotland is – at least for now – on a very different trajectory than England when it comes to the social protection of its population.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guns &amp; Butter - The Post 9/11 Era</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/the-post-9-11-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 19:33:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/the-post-9-11-era/</guid>
      <description>Posted on September 30th, 2019
Guest: Michel Chossudovsky
We discuss the broader geopolitical ramifications of the September 11th terrorist attacks, including the attack on Afghanistan, the Global War on Terror, and the Western Military Alliance support for the terrorists; attack on Afghanistan prepared long before 9&amp;frasl;11; Osama bin Laden an intelligence asset; Bushes, et.al., business partners with the bin Ladens; earlier history of Afghanistan before the Soviet intervention; Afghanistan becoming a modern nation; US imperialism the destroyer of countries; assassination of the leader of the Northern Alliance, Ahmad Shah Massoud; the cultivation of opium poppy; Afghanistan a major transport corridor for oil and gas; mineral resources; Islamic fundamentalism a strategy of US intelligence to indoctrinate and recruit jihadists; extension of al Qaeda worldwide; US losing control of Afghanistan and Pakistan to China; pre-emptive nuclear war doctrine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UK - More than a million welfare benefit sanctions imposed against disabled people</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/uk-more-than-a-million-welfare-benefit-sanctions-imposed-against-disabled-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 13:25:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/news/uk-more-than-a-million-welfare-benefit-sanctions-imposed-against-disabled-people/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By Dennis Moore
13 March 2018&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New data reveals the relentless attack on disabled benefit claimants in the last decade. The study found that more than 900,000 Job Seeker’s Allowance (JSA) claimants, who reported a disability, have been financially sanctioned since May 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also sanctioned were 110,000 claimants of Employment and Support Allowance (ESA), a benefit paid to someone who is sick, and placed in the “work related activity group” (WRAG). A further 140,000 sanctions were applied, but later cancelled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A sanction is applied to someone’s benefit when a claimant is deemed not to have met part of the stated “conditionality” for claiming that benefit. This can include missing an appointment, or not applying for enough jobs in a given time scale.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>