<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>War on </title>
    <link>/categories/war/</link>
    <description>Recent content in War on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 21:57:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/war/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Remembering the Odessa Massacre the Politics of Post Maidan Ukraine</title>
      <link>/news/remembering-the-odessa-massacre-the-politics-of-post-maidan-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 21:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/remembering-the-odessa-massacre-the-politics-of-post-maidan-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>On May 2, 2014, at least 42 people were killed in Odessa, Ukraine when the Trade Unions House building was set on fire following clashes which occurred in the wake of the Maidan coup which occurred earlier that year. Phil Wilayto, Editor of the Quarterly Newspaper &amp;lsquo;The Virginia Defender &amp;amp; Coordinator of the Odessa Solidarity Campaign, joins the show to discuss the details of this event and the lack of justice for its perpetrators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roger Waters - on - RT - The Us and Uk Are Trying to Kill Julian Assange</title>
      <link>/news/roger-waters-on-rt-the-us-and-uk-are-trying-to-kill-julian-assange/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 14:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/roger-waters-on-rt-the-us-and-uk-are-trying-to-kill-julian-assange/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By Kevin Reed
2 November 2019&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Famed rock music artist Roger Waters gave an extensive and significant interview to the television network Russia Today (RT) on October 25 in which he denounced the continued illegal imprisonment of Julian Assange and reiterated his call for the freedom of the WikiLeaks publisher and founder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Julian Assange, who founded WikiLeaks in 2006 and published extensive proof of US war crimes in the Middle East and other corruption around the world, is currently being held at Belmarsh prison in London. Although he has broken no laws and not been convicted of any crime, Assange is being held in advance of being handed over—in blatant contravention of international law—to the United States to face 18 charges, including violation of the Espionage Act of 1917.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guns &amp; Butter - Exposing the 9/11 Deception - Christopher Bollyn</title>
      <link>/news/exposing-the-9-11-deception-christopher-bollyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 13:09:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/exposing-the-9-11-deception-christopher-bollyn/</guid>
      <description>Christopher Bollyn in NYC on 9&amp;frasl;11; companies hired to do ground zero &amp;ldquo;clean-up&amp;rdquo;; hot spots; analysis of nuclear footprint at ground zero; analysis of smoke and the particle effect that caused debilitating illnesses in NYC; the mysterious &amp;ldquo;final load&amp;rdquo; moved out of ground zero; same criminal network behind 9&amp;frasl;11 and Jeffrey Epstein; Ronald Lauder; privatization programs; Ehud Barak; University of Alaska Fairbanks study on WTC 7; Commissioner of the Franklin Square and Munson Fire District calling for a new investigation; government officials conduct the cover-up; Khalid Sheikh Mohammed; surveillance state; dystopia created by 9&amp;frasl;11 attacks; motivation of 9&amp;frasl;11 to create the war on terror; Bollyn&amp;rsquo;s new book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guns &amp; Butter - The Post 9/11 Era</title>
      <link>/news/the-post-9-11-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 19:33:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/the-post-9-11-era/</guid>
      <description>Posted on September 30th, 2019
Guest: Michel Chossudovsky
We discuss the broader geopolitical ramifications of the September 11th terrorist attacks, including the attack on Afghanistan, the Global War on Terror, and the Western Military Alliance support for the terrorists; attack on Afghanistan prepared long before 9&amp;frasl;11; Osama bin Laden an intelligence asset; Bushes, et.al., business partners with the bin Ladens; earlier history of Afghanistan before the Soviet intervention; Afghanistan becoming a modern nation; US imperialism the destroyer of countries; assassination of the leader of the Northern Alliance, Ahmad Shah Massoud; the cultivation of opium poppy; Afghanistan a major transport corridor for oil and gas; mineral resources; Islamic fundamentalism a strategy of US intelligence to indoctrinate and recruit jihadists; extension of al Qaeda worldwide; US losing control of Afghanistan and Pakistan to China; pre-emptive nuclear war doctrine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>