<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dr. Jack Rasmus on Peter&#39;s weblog</title>
    <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/tags/dr.-jack-rasmus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dr. Jack Rasmus on Peter&#39;s weblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 11:48:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/tags/dr.-jack-rasmus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Guns &amp; Butter - After Trump and Neoliberalism - What&#39;s Next Dr. Jack Rasmus</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/post/guns-and-butter-after-trump-and-neoliberalism-whats-next-dr-jack-rasmus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 11:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/post/guns-and-butter-after-trump-and-neoliberalism-whats-next-dr-jack-rasmus/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Jack Rasmus discusses the last three chapters of his new book, “The Scourge of Neoliberalism: From Reagan to Trump” with a focus on the growing contradictions within the Neoliberal policy regime in the 21st Century; the deep technological and material forces undermining and driving the contradictions; and why the 2020s decade will require yet another, fourth restructuring of US capitalism that may fundamentally differ from the Neoliberal experience of the past four decades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guns &amp; Butter - Neoliberalism From Expansion to Stagnation Dr. Jack Rasmus</title>
      <link>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/post/guns-and-butter-neoliberalism-from-expansion-to-stagnation-dr-jack-rasmus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 11:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beesgo.github.io/weblog/post/guns-and-butter-neoliberalism-from-expansion-to-stagnation-dr-jack-rasmus/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Jack Rasmus discusses his newest book, &amp;ldquo;The Scourge of Neoliberalism: US Economic Policy from Reagan to Trump&amp;rdquo;, with an emphasis on the practice of neoliberalism as opposed to the economic ideology which obscures its class basis; neoliberalism as the third major capitalist restructuring of the 20th century as a response to the crisis of capitalism in the 1970s; the four economic policy areas, i.e., fiscal, monetary, industrial and external, that require restructuring as capitalism evolves into a new crisis; the fallacies of neoliberalism; government policy encourages offshoring of US manufacturing; global dollar recycling into US treasuries to support the twin US deficits solution; financialization of the economy; shadow banking; deregulation and privatization; neoliberalism socially destructive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>