<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scotland on </title>
    <link>/tags/scotland/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scotland on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 15:15:17 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/scotland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welfare state alive in scotland but waning elsewhere - UN poverty expert</title>
      <link>/news/welfare-state-alive-in-scotland-but-waning-elsewhere-un-poverty-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 15:15:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/welfare-state-alive-in-scotland-but-waning-elsewhere-un-poverty-expert/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A UN poverty expert has said Scotland is on “a very different trajectory” to the rest of the UK when it comes to social security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Philip Alston, UN Special Rapporteur on extreme poverty and human rights, said the “spirit” of the welfare state is “alive and humming” north of the border, but is “waning” elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The international human rights law professor visited the UK last year to produce a report which found policies of austerity introduced in 2010 were continuing to have “tragic social consequences”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It also claimed the Scottish government’s attempts to reduce the impact of social security changes – such as the two-child benefit cap – were not sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking at an event at the University of Edinburgh, he said: “Scotland is spending a lot of money on mitigation, mitigating measures that they see as the least humane policies that come from London.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“All of this indicates that Scotland is – at least for now – on a very different trajectory than England when it comes to the social protection of its population.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>